{
    "nivel": "Tablas de multiplicacion",
    "secciones": [
      {
        "seccion": "Tabla 1",
        "etapas": [
          { "etapa": 1, "preguntas": [ 
            {
                "pregunta": "1 x 1",
                "respuesta": 1,
                "opciones": [0, 2, 3, 1]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "1 x 8",
                "respuesta": 8,
                "opciones": [7, 6, 5, 8]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "1 x 2",
                "respuesta": 2,
                "opciones": [3, 1, 2, 4]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "3 + 1",
                "respuesta": 3,
                "opciones": [1, 3, 4, 5]
              }   
          ] },
          { "etapa": 2, "preguntas": [ 
            {
                "pregunta": "4 x 1",
                "respuesta": 4,
                "opciones": [6, 4, 3, 5]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "1 x 3",
                "respuesta": 3,
                "opciones": [5, 2, 6, 3]
              },
              {
                "pregunta": "7 x 1",
                "respuesta": 7,
                "opciones": [8, 6, 5, 7]
              }
          ] }
        ]
      },
      {
        "seccion": "Tabla 2",
        "etapas": [
            { "etapa": 1, "preguntas": [ 
                {
                    "pregunta": "2 x 4",
                    "respuesta": 8,
                    "opciones": [2, 8, 7, 6]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "6 x 2",
                    "respuesta": 12,
                    "opciones": [4, 12, 8, 10]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "2 x 1",
                    "respuesta": 2,
                    "opciones": [2, 3, 1, 4]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "10 x 2",
                    "respuesta": 20,
                    "opciones": [12, 20, 16, 18]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "4 x 2",
                    "respuesta": 8,
                    "opciones": [7, 6, 8, 5]
                  }
              ] },
              { "etapa": 2, "preguntas": [ 
                {
                    "pregunta": "2 x 9",
                    "respuesta": 18,
                    "opciones": [10, 16, 11, 18]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "2 x 5",
                    "respuesta": 10,
                    "opciones": [10, 9, 11, 8]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "2 x 6",
                    "respuesta": 12,
                    "opciones": [10, 12, 11, 8]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "9 x 2",
                    "respuesta": 18,
                    "opciones": [14, 19, 11, 18]
                  },
                  {
                    "pregunta": "7 x 2",
                    "respuesta": 14,
                    "opciones": [14, 16, 9, 10]
                  }
              ] }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }